https://www.hist.cam.ac.uk/site-privacy-cookie-policies

Skip to main content
Site Privacy & Cookie Policies
Privacy Notice
Introduction
This page explains what personal information we gather when you visit this web site.
Who will process my personal information?
The information published here applies to the use of your personal information (also known as 'personal data') by the University of Cambridge through the viewing or use of this site.
General personal information collected on our websites
When you visit any of the websites within the Cambridge domain we hold certain information about you for service and security reasons. For more information on this, please see https://www.cam.ac.uk/about-this-site/privacy-policy
Further information
For more information about how we handle your personal information, and your rights under data protection legislation, please see https://www.information-compliance.admin.cam.ac.uk/data-protection/general-data
Cookies
Users who visit this site may receive some or all of the Google Analytics cookies if the site administrator has enabled them (whether or not they authenticate).
The site may embed third-party material (e.g. YouTube videos) and these may carry their own cookies. You must refer to the site's local cookie policy to determine what cookies are being set and for what purpose.
The site may include 'ShareThis' social media buttons, which will carry cookies if the user has a 'ShareThis' account enabled.
Users who authenticate will receive cookies from the Raven/Shibboleth authentication system.
Raven privacy & cookie policy:http://raven.cam.ac.uk/privacy.html
Google analytics cookie policy:http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html
Navigate
